[{"question": " hey! babe! aren&#146;t you excited we&#146;re going on our honeymoon?", "answer": " yeah i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  bermuda, bahama, come on pretty mama&#133;", "answer": " that&#146;s right. get it out of your system while we&#146;re alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " yeah! have a great honeymoon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i&#146;d better go pack.", "answer": " oh no, i already packed. the only thing i couldn&#146;t find though was your speedo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  oh good you&#146;re still here!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " and i also wanted you guys to know that i am telling the father today.  what? what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " we know its ross!", "answer": " how?! how do you know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " it was his sweater, but&#151;oh my god!", "answer": " oh, i so wanted ross to know first, but i&#146;m so relieved you guys know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " this is so great! and i&#146;m gonna be your baby&#146;s aunt!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  you&#146;re all gonna be aunts and uncles.", "answer": " yeah, but i&#146;m the only one related by blood.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " okay. great! so now that you guys all know you can help me. give me some advice on how i&#146;m gonna tell ross!", "answer": " well, what were you gonna say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " well i was gonna tell him that i&#146;m-i&#146;m gonna have the baby and he can be as involved as he wants.", "answer": " well that, that sounds good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey! good luck!", "answer": " yeah, bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  hey, what was that all about?", "answer": " well i guess there is no harm in telling you now, rachel and ross are gonna have a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  what?! i didn&#146;t even know that&#151;why didn&#146;t you tell me?!  why am i talking like this?!", "answer": " i didn&#146;t think you could keep it a secret.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  what?!  i am an excellent secret keeper. i have kept all of our secrets.", "answer": " what secrets?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  you&#146;ll tell me later?", "answer": " you already know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, it's so romantic to send people off on their honeymoon.", "answer": " y&#146;know, monica and chandler are married. ross and rachel are having a baby. maybe you and i should do something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " all in good time my love. all in good time. oh shoot! i left my guitar in their apartment. well you can let me in later.", "answer": " i don&#146;t have a key, they took mine to give to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " what?! they took mine to give to you!", "answer": " why would they take away our keys?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " maybe they don&#146;t trust us.", "answer": " no that&#146;s not it. they let me keep my key the last time they were out of town.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " you mean the time you broke the ketchup bottle and cleaned it up with monica&#146;s guest towels?", "answer": " hey, i washed those!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no you didn&#146;t.", "answer": " yeah that didn&#146;t sound like me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well, what am i gonna do? i really need my guitar!", "answer": " yeah, i have stuff in there too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what stuff?", "answer": " monica&#146;s chicken parm! i&#146;ll take care of it.  hey mr. treeger, it&#146;s joey tribbiani. listen, i need to get into monica and chandler&#146;s apartment. it&#146;s an emergency.  uhh, gas leak! yeah oh, and bring garlic bread.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " did rachel find you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " no why?", "answer": " oh she was looking for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh well, i guess i&#146;ll catch up with her later.", "answer": " well, she really wanted to talk to you now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yeah, it seemed pretty important.", "answer": " oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i think i might know what this is about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah. uh, uh we promised we weren&#146;t gonna tell anybody this but uh, about a month ago rachel and i slept together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  and?", "answer": " wow! i thought you would be a little more shocked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh sorry.  and?!", "answer": " well, we-we said we&#146;d just do it that one time but, but now i think she may wanna start things up again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah, i don&#146;t think that&#146;s what it is.", "answer": " why? what-what else could it be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh wow, i don&#146;t feel well.", "answer": " i&#146;m telling you. i&#146;m telling you. that&#146;s what it is. no wonder she was looking at me all funny during the wedding. she didn&#146;t say anything to you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  maybe it&#146;s something you ate?", "answer": " please, just-just, just go and talk to rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " they&#146;re kissing let&#146;s just go around them.", "answer": " oh honey, leave them alone, they&#146;re in love.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i&#146;m in love too! but in an orderly fashion.", "answer": " next?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " sorry. we didn&#146;t hear you; we&#146;re on our honeymoon.", "answer": " oh, let me see what i can do.  there are some first class seats available.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  did you hear that?! they bumped them up to first class because they are on their honeymoon! come on! let&#146;s act like we&#146;re on our honeymoon.", "answer": " we are on our honeymoon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " grab my ass!", "answer": " next?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " hi, sorry. i almost didn&#146;t hear you, because y&#146;know i&#146;m just so in love with my new husband. we&#146;re on our honeymoon.", "answer": " congratulations. okay, mr. bing you&#146;ll be in 25j and mrs. bing you&#146;ll be in 25k.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh no, you see we&#146;re on our honeymoon. so umm, can you do your little thing and bump us up to first class?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, all our first class seats are taken. that couple got the last two.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " you see, if we&#146;d gone around them like i said, we&#151;she would&#146;ve given us those tickets. damnit!", "answer": " 25j and k, any chance those aren&#146;t together?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i still can&#146;t believe they took away my key. you trust me with yours.", "answer": " of course i do! and i&#146;m gonna give it back to you as soon as they&#146;re done with it at the key shining place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what the hell is that? (they go into the hallway and see mr. treeger watching one of new york&#146;s bravest breakdown monica and chandler&#146;s door with an ax.]", "answer": " whoa! whoa! whoa! treeger, what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " you said there was a gas leak in here.", "answer": " well why don&#146;t you use your key?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " look at that! look at that! they&#146;re going into the first class lounge! do you know what they have in there?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " just act like you belong.", "answer": " oh my god! oranges!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " uh sir, may i see your tickets please?", "answer": " yes, of course.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, would you move your thumb? i can&#146;t see the seat number.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s all right, i have it memorized. it&#146;s 1a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  sir, this is not a first class ticket. i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " apology accepted. excuse us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " sir! i&#146;m afraid i&#146;m gonna have to ask you to leave.", "answer": " fine.  go! go! go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " hi.  umm, i think there&#146;s something that we really need to talk about.", "answer": "  i think we do. why don&#146;t we go inside?  look uh, i know why you&#146;re here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " you do?", "answer": " yeah, and to save you from any embarrassment umm, i think maybe i should talk first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  okay.", "answer": " okay.  uh, ross and rachel. rachel and ross. that&#146;s been one heck of a see-saw hasn&#146;t it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " i mean look, that-that one night we had was fun and&#133;and certainly passionate, but don&#146;t you think it&#146;s better if we just stayed friends?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " seriously. what?!", "answer": " okay. okay. y&#146;know what? if you want to, we can do it one more time. i mean i&#146;d-i&#146;d be okay with that. in fact, i have some time right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " okay, y&#146;know what? can i, can i talk now?", "answer": " oh sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  can i get you some water?", "answer": " i&#146;m good. i&#146;m good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah, i need uh&#133; i&#146;m just&#151;i don&#146;t know&#151;i don&#146;t understand, umm, how this happened? we-we used a condom.", "answer": " i know. i know, but y&#146;know condoms only work like 97% of the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " what? what? what?!! well they should put that on the box!!!", "answer": " they do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " no they don&#146;t!!!  well they should put it in huge black letters!!!!", "answer": " okay ross come on let&#146;s just forget about the condoms.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh well i may as well have!", "answer": " listen, y&#146;know what? i was really freaked out too when i found out&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " freaked out? hey no, i&#146;m not freaked out! i&#146;m indignant! as a consumer!", "answer": " y&#146;know what? let&#146;s, let&#146;s talk later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " no! no! i want to talk now! okay? i&#151;in fact,  i am going to talk to the president of the condom company!", "answer": " okay, y&#146;know maybe i should come back&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  shh! shh! shh!", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i&#146;ve looked everywhere. there&#146;s no gas leak.", "answer": "  huh. so then i can heat this up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " anyway uh, i&#146;ll get moving on that new door.", "answer": " oh great! and listen, could you do us a favor and not tell chandler and monica about this? &#145;cause y&#146;know umm, they don&#146;t-they don&#146;t have any kids of their own and-and this door was like a child to them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well i&#146;m gonna have to put on a new lock, they&#146;ll find out anyway.", "answer": " oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  whoa! this looks like an all day job, i&#146;ll have to cancel my yoga class.  hey ross!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " could you tell jasmine that i won't make it to yoga class today?", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh my god! what happened to the door?!", "answer": " so it&#146;s noticeable huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " look, is rachel here? i really need to talk to her.", "answer": " didn&#146;t you two already talk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah but uh&#133; okay, okay look you guys know that rachel and i slept together, but there&#146;s something else.  rachel&#146;s pregnant.", "answer": "  oh my god!!! i can&#146;t believe that!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  holy mother of god!!!", "answer": " with my child.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " that is brand new information!!", "answer": " you already know don&#146;t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " a little bit.", "answer": " how are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " okay. okay. i mean i&#146;ll be okay. it&#146;s just i don&#146;t think i handled it very well.", "answer": " well, what did you say to her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " nothing. but the complaint department at the condom company got an earful. and then when i turned around she was gone.", "answer": " oh ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " but hey, in my defense i-i just found out condoms are like only 97% effective.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i gotta go find her.", "answer": " whoa! hey! whoa!! hold up! are you serious?! so like 3% of the time they don&#146;t even work?! huh? they should put that on the box!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " evidently they do.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe we&#146;re here.", "answer": " oh you&#146;ve got to be kidding me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " what?  front desk clerk: as a wedding gift to you, the hotel would like to give you the honeymoon suite.", "answer": " no!! you have been screwing us all day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " who are you?", "answer": " we&#146;re you just ten seconds later!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yeah! you already got the first class tickets; you got the lounge! i mean we should get free stuff too! i mean you&#146;re not the only ones on your honeymoon!", "answer": " well you can have the suite if you want. we don&#146;t care about where we stay. we&#146;re here to celebrate our love together. we don&#146;t have to get free stuff. we just want to be together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " hey monica it&#146;s joey. listen uh, phoebe and i smell gas comin&#146; from your apartment.", "answer": " what? are you serious?!  joey smells gas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what else is new?", "answer": " yeah and we&#146;d go check it out, but you took away our keys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " well do something! get in there!", "answer": " how? i guess i could break down your door.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yeah! do that!", "answer": " and-and you won&#146;t blame us for any damage?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " no!  are you doing it?! i don&#146;t hear anything! come on!", "answer": " uh, okay i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll break it down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " okay rachel, are you comfortable?", "answer": "  if i said i was, would you judge me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " the doctor will be here in a minute to do your sonogram.", "answer": " okay.  oh man, i swear if they sold these at pottery barn&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " uh we-we need to talk.", "answer": " uh-uh-uh, right now? because i&#146;ve kinda got an el fresco situation going on over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " please, please i want to apologize for the way i acted earlier today.", "answer": " okay ross that&#146;s fine, but can you please stand near my head?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what? oh yeah.  i&#146;m sorry. i mean i-i think i went a little crazy. i mean i was thinking about myself when i  really&#151;i should have been thinking about you rach&#133;", "answer": " okay. head ross! head ross! head ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " right! right! i just&#151;i want you to know that i&#146;m going to be there through this whole thing, okay? okay? the doctor&#146;s appointments, the uh, the lamaze classes, uh baby-proofing the apartment&#151;although we could probably worry about that &#145;til after we get married.", "answer": " what married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well yeah, i think we should get married.", "answer": " what, because that&#146;s your answer to everything?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " no, because that&#146;s the right thing to do.", "answer": " yeah, maybe if you&#146;re in love. but ross, we are not in love, are", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no but&#133;but still you can&#146;t possibly do this alone.", "answer": " excuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " come on rach, you can&#146;t even eat alone in a restaurant.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i&#146;m just saying if you can&#146;t eat by yourself, how do you expect to have a baby by yourself?", "answer": " i can too eat by myself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " when have you ever?", "answer": " when certain people leave the table and i am not finished!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " well certain other people take two hours to eat a bowl of soup!", "answer": " oh please, you inhale your food!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i grew up with monica! if you didn&#146;t eat fast you didn&#146;t eat!!", "answer": "  am i interrupting?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " oh no dr. long, please come in. this is ross, he is the father.", "answer": " but not the husband, because evidently she can do this alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " huh. nice to meet you. i&#146;ll get started on this.", "answer": "  i don&#146;t know why you can&#146;t admit that you need me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i do need you! i need you to stand near my head!", "answer": " okay, everything looks good. here it is on the screen.  here is your uterus. and right here is your baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh my god.", "answer": " wow. there it is, i see it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " congratulations. i&#146;ll give you two a minute.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " pretty amazing huh?", "answer": " i don&#146;t see it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what? what?!", "answer": " i can&#146;t see it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " you-you just said that you did!", "answer": " i know, i lied! i didn&#146;t want her to think i was a terrible mother! i can&#146;t even see my own baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " oh sure, come here!  sure you can! uh, look come here look,  it&#146;s-it&#146;s-it&#146;s, it&#146;s right there .", "answer": " oh. oh, it&#146;s beautiful. i see it now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " do you really?", "answer": " no, i don&#146;t see it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " come on! come on! here, okay-okay, you see this?  this tiny thing that looks like a peanut?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " sweetie that&#146;s it.", "answer": " that&#146;s it? well i saw that! ohh-ohh-oh, thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " you&#146;re welcome.", "answer": " wow! i can&#146;t believe that&#146;s our baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " hey! so how was the doctor?", "answer": " oh, everything went great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " good.", "answer": " oh hey, show them the picture of your uterus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " i don&#146;t see the baby. where is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " oh no, i know i couldn&#146;t see it either at first, but it&#146;s right umm&#133;  ross, i lost it again.", "answer": " oh. (he takes the picture and hugs her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}]